articlechanger.net 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Article Changer - The World's #1 FREE Article Spinner!

### Information we gather

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address

### How we use the information we gather

Your personal information will not be shared with any third party.  
We use basic analytics software to track general site visitor usage.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible only by the website owner.

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we store all of our data on a secure server, protected by the latest hardware and software security solutions.  
Our systems are tested regularly to ensure that your information is protected by hackers and viruses.

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
